(Amy:)Sorry, we've cut the monkeys down
to one cigarette a day...
(Amy:)...so things are a little intense.
(Amy:)Makes me miss my marijuana-abusing
flatworms. Those guys were mellow.
(Sheldon:)Good news, uh, the latest episode
of Fun With Flags is online.
- Oh, that's right. How'd it go with Penny?
- Much better than I expected.
(Sheldon:)She even gave me some helpful tips
about acting and body language.
(Sheldon:)Watch.
(Sheldon:)Welcome to my world.
(Sheldon:)Not welcome to my world.
(Sheldon:)Welcome.
Not welcome.
(Amy:)Subtle but powerful.
(Sheldon:)I know, I'm still learning to control it.
(Amy:)Did you tell Penny how helpful she was?
(Sheldon:)Why would I do that?
(Amy:)Because she's your friend
and she did a nice job.
(Amy:)I'm sure she'd like to hear it.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Amy:)I didn't mean now. Hello?